lemonfree.com 2011-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Lemon Free Classifieds

Sign Up / Login to LemonFree.com

**This statement describes our practices with respect to visitors to LemonFree.com (the "Site"). It describes the extent of our responsibilities and visitors to this Site are deemed to accept it. Please review it carefully.**

At LemonFree.com we respect your privacy. We will use our best efforts to ensure that your information is secure and only used for the purposes for which you have consented. 

LemonFree.com only collects personal information from you if you are listing a vehicle.  When listing a vehicle the only personal information you are required to provide is your email address.  However, you have the option of providing more personal information in order to provide more than one means to contact you.

LemonFree.com does collect anonymous information about visitors to the Site.  This information is used internally to perform traffic analysis. 

LemonFree.com only collects personal information about you with your specific knowledge.  If you list a vehicle, you are asked to provide an email address for contact purposes and you have the option of providing telephone numbers or text messaging numbers as additional contact information.  When you provide us with your personal information, you consent and agree to our use and disclosure of your personal information for the following purposes:

  * to provide the service you have requested, and to operate our business, as described in this Privacy Policy; 
  * to enable potential buyers to contact you; and
  * to offer you more information about our services and the services of affiliates (If you opt in to such use and disclosure).

## Disclosure of Your Information

Any personal information provided by you will only be disclosed with your consent.  For example, when you list a vehicle, you have the option of posting your email address.  If you choose not to, your email address will be kept confidential and potential buyers can contact you through LemonFree.com’s instant messaging system.

If, as a Seller, you opt to publish your email address or other contact information on the Site, you acknowledge that such information will be available to any visitor to our Site. As such, we cannot control how visitors will use your contact information.   For example, visitors may use your email address to send you unsolicited emails that LemonFree.com will not be able to stop.   You should also remember that your personal information will continue to be available on the Internet until you delist your listing. You may discontinue your listing by delisting the listing at LemonFree.com

## Amending Personal Information

As a visitor, you may also make corrections or updates to the personal information that you provide us.  With respect to your personal contact information, you make changes online.  When making changes online, simply click "Edit Listing" on the LemonFree.com home page, enter your Login and Password, click "Login”.  _Please note that this information will be located on a secure site._     

## Use of Website Tracking and Cookies

An Internet Protocol (“ **IP** ”) address is a unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are on the Internet. LemonFree.com collects IP addresses for the purposes of: helping us diagnose problems with our computers, for administrative purposes, to report aggregated information, and to audit the use of our Site. 

Although, we do not link personal information to your IP address, by using this Site, you acknowledge that we may use IP addresses to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, Site, visitors, or others. 

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that a website you visit sends to your computer for record-keeping purposes.  Cookies are stored in a file on your computer’s hard drive and are used to make your use of website simpler for you by saving your preferences.   LemonFree.com uses these preferences to make our Site more intuitive to use when you return to the Site. Cookies do not identify you personally unless you have chosen to provide personal information to us. 

LemonFree.com also uses third party third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. These companies may use information about your visits to this Site (not including your name, address, or other personal information) to provide advertisements on this Site, other sites and other media about goods and services that may be of interest to you.. In providing advertisements, a unique third party cookie may be placed on your browser. You may also get cookies from such advertisers if you use the links on our Site to reach their respective websites. LemonFree.com does not control or have access to these cookies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

## Changes to this Policy

LemonFree.com may be required to revise this Privacy Policy from time to time and you agree that LemonFree.com may do so at any time, by updating this posting.  LemonFree.com may revise this Privacy Policy by means of a notice on the Site and you agree that such changes will take effect after the revised Privacy Policy is posted on the Site. Continued use of the Site after such changes are posted will signify your agreement to these revised terms.  You should visit this page periodically to review this Privacy Policy.

## Possible Future Uses of Information

In the unlikely event that another company acquires the assets of LemonFree.com, information on our visitors/Sellers would be among the transferred assets. 

## E-mail Communications

We collect and store your email address from any communications that you may send to LemonFree.com by clicking on any of the email links. We may use your email address to communicate with you, if your email indicates that a response to your inquiry is requested or to address a concern or complaint you may have. ****

If you wish to contact us to: 

  * inquire about our privacy practices; 
  * provide feedback and comments; 
  * access or correct your personal information we have; and/or
  * opt out of further communications, contact us as detailed below.

Email: [privacyofficer@LemonFree.com](mailto:privacyofficer@LemonFree.com)

This site contains links to other sites. LemonFree.com **** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
